http://www.palmbeachzoo.org/donor-privacy-policy

Dual Discovery Pass
Nature Play Pavilion, Play Fountain, Kid Zone, Tropics Cafe, Gift Shop
Search
Enter your search term and press enter. Press Esc or X to close.
Updated: 8/20
Palm Beach Zoo & Conservation Society is committed to protecting the privacy of our donors and prospective donors.
Purpose
As a 501(c)(3) nonprofit, Palm Beach Zoo & Conservation Society relies on generous support from donations in order to fulfill our mission. The purpose of Palm Beach Zoo’s Donor Privacy Policy is to uphold the trust and confidence of donors and prospective donors to our organization through transparency on the Zoo’s practices and policies for data collection, use, and protection relating to donations.
Policy Summary
Palm Beach Zoo is committed to protecting the privacy of our donors. We hold donor information in the strictest confidence and will not sell, trade or share a donor’s personal information with any outside party. All donations to Palm Beach Zoo are tax-exempt. Should you have any questions with regard to this policy, please contact Karen Carr, Chief Development Officer.
Privacy Across All Platforms
This policy applies to all information received by Palm Beach Zoo, both online and offline, across any digital platform or application as well as any electronic, written or oral communications with staff or Palm Beach Zoo representatives.
Consent
The Zoo’s Donor Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use and protection of data and information. By submitting information as part of a donation, you give your consent to the terms and conditions of the policy for the purposes stated below.
Collecting and Storing Information
Palm Beach Zoo ethically collects and securely stores any personally identifiable information that you have provided us. Information may be collected when a donor or prospective donor makes an inquiry or contribution via email, website or phone, interfaces with Zoo staff, board or representatives or registers for a Zoo event, either on Zoo property or at an outside location.
The categories of personal information we collect and store may include:
Full name
Physical address(es)
Telephone number(s)
Email address
Other identifying information
This represents only a few examples of personal information that may be collected by Palm Beach Zoo. From time to time, the Zoo may collect other personal information in ways not described above.
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information
Palm Beach Zoo utilizes personal information and data to maintain records of donations, send acknowledgements, mail year-end tax statements, send newsletters and direct mail pieces as well as for internal marketing purposes. Palm Beach Zoo will not sell, trade or share your personal information. Payment information, such as credit card or banking information is not stored in our system.
Donor Recognition
Donor contributions may be recognized or published in donor recognition materials produced by the Zoo, including print, verbal acknowledgment and/or on digital media. If you do not wish for your name to appear in these materials or be published, please contact Karen Carr, Chief Development Officer.
Future Privacy Policy Changes
Palm Beach Zoo reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time.
Thank you for your support of Palm Beach Zoo & Conservation Society.
Alert: Zoo Lights tickets must be purchased in advance.
They will not be available at the gate.
For the latest COVID safety information CLICK HERE!
